SADIE SOUTHWORTH

802-798-2206 sadie.southworth@gmail.com

817 Pine St, Apt 311, Burlington VT, 05401

PROFILE

Detail-oriented worker with 5+ years working in the hospitality industry. Now seeking the opportunity to contribute my extensive customer service and interpersonal skills to a strong organization that values hard working employees and who also offer opportunities for continued growth.

EXPERIENCE

COSTUMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE, ONION RIVER ANIMAL HOSPITAL; BERLIN, VT – AUGUST 2018-SEPTEMBER 2020. APRIL 2021-CURRENT

As a CSR (costumer service representative) it is my duty to answer all incoming calls, greet costumers when they walk through the door, maintain a clean and organized working environment, take payment, and assist clients with their respective needs. I have also worked as a technician assistant which included responsibilities of taking vitals, giving vaccines, drawing blood, medical data entry, and adding to SOAP notes. These positions have enhanced my interpersonal and situational adaptability skills. It has also taught me phone etiquette, cash handling skills, and has assisted in bettering my organization skills, costumer service, and computer system skills.

CUSTOMER CARE SPECIALIST, PEAK VETERINARY REFERRAL CENTER; WILLISTON, VT – OCTOBER 2020-APRIL 2021

My role as a customer care specialist is in an office setting where I am the first point of contact between clients and the business. In this role my responsibilities are answering incoming phone calls, responding to emails, inputting client and patient data, collecting and running payment information, and being a point of contact between clients and the rest of the hospital. This position has strengthened my problem solving abilities, time management skills (especially during busy times of the day), and has honed my proficiency in effective communication. This work requires me to work in team and individual settings, and to interact with many individuals throughout the company and to adapt to each persons needs.

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT (TEMPORARY), TIMBER LANE PEDIATRICS; SOUTH BURLINGTON, VT – SEPTEMBER 2020-JANUARY 2021

As an administrative assistant my main responsibilities included scheduling patients, collections out reach, registration, processing health insurance, and online portal help/

activation. These duties have strengthened my multitasking skills, organizational skills, and computer system/telephone skills.

SUPPORT STAFF, DOC PONDS; STOWE, VT - AUGUST 2015-APRIL 2018 In this position my primary responsibility was hostessing. I also provided support with running food, bar-backing, keeping the restaurant clean and presentable, and training new staff. This position has taught me superior customer service skills, time management, organization and how to work successfully in a stressful, high pace environment.

COUNTER STAFF, SKINNY PANCAKE; STOWE, VT - DECEMBER 2017-JANUARY 2018 Counter staff at Skinny Pancake included greeting guests, taking orders and payments, running food, and bussing tables. I kept restaurant clean, stocked, and organized. This position expanded my current skills by working more closely with payments and a computer system. This position also taught me how to focus on multiple responsibilities and how to organize tasks due to urgency.

FRONT DESK TICKET SELLER, STOWE MOUNTAIN RESORT; STOWE, VT - NOVEMBER 2016- JAN 2017

For this position my main responsibilities were answering the phones, selling tickets/using a computer system to do so, helping guests choose the right product for them, filing paperwork, filling out paperwork, sorting through issues that guests are having with their passes, and keeping guests happy and fulfilling their needs.

EDUCATION

PEOPLES ACADEMY HIGH SCHOOL, GRADUATE 2015 UNIVERSITY OF VERMONT, YEAR 1

REFERENCES

